freeticketclassifieds.com 2017-08-02

# Tickifieds Privacy Policy

Tickifieds is committed to safeguarding your online privacy. The following policy outlines how your personal information will be treated as you use our website.

Tickifieds may update this privacy policy from time to time, in order to take into account new laws and technology or to reflect changes in our operations. All personal information held by Tickifieds.com will be governed by Tickifieds's most recent policy which will be displayed on this site.

## 1\. What personal information do we collect?

Tickifieds primarily collects personal information from its users during the registration process. We collect and store users' names, email addresses, contact numbers and usernames and also other information including user's IP addresses and standard web log information. If a user contacts Tickifieds via email, a record of that correspondence may also be stored.

Tickifieds may place a cookie in the browser files of a user's computer. We use cookies to save information you give us so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. This allows us to personalize the site to your taste and provide the best web experience possible to our users. We do not use cookies to track your movements on different web sites and do not exchange cookies with other entities.

## 2\. How do we use your personal information?

Tickifieds uses the information collected to:

**Provide the products or services requested;  
**Communicate with our users;  
**Manage and enhance our services;  
**Resolve disputes and troubleshooting;  
**Measure interest in our services.

## 3\. Disclosure

Tickifieds may provide your information to law enforcement to aid in their investigations of illegal or fraudulent postings. If Tickifieds sells part or all of its business, personal information may be part of the assets transferred to the purchaser.

## 4\. How do we treat sensitive information?

"Sensitive Information" means information relating to a person's racial or ethnic origin, membership of political bodies, religion, membership of a trade union or professional or trade association, sexual preferences, criminal record and health.

Tickifieds may use and disclose sensitive information only for the purpose for which it was provided or a directly related secondary purpose or as allowed by law unless you have agreed otherwise.

## 5\. Management and security of personal information

Tickifieds protects the personal information it holds from misuse, loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure by various means including password access and secure servers. Only the administrators of Tickifieds and the user have access to that user's personal information. We recommend that users do not disclose their password to anyone.

## 6\. Updating personal information

Tickifieds endeavours to ensure that the personal information it holds is accurate, complete and up-to-date. Users can update their information after logging in. Alternatively, users can email [admin@tickifieds.com](mailto:admin@tickifieds.com) to advise of their information updates. Where personal information is no longer required by Tickifieds, it will be destroyed or de-identified.

## 7\. How to access personal information Tickifieds holds about you

You have the right to seek access to the personal information held about you and to advise Tickifieds of any inaccuracy. There are some exceptions to this right set out in the Privacy Act.

If you make an access request, Tickifieds will ask you to verify your identity and specify what information you require. Tickifieds may charge a fee to cover the costs of meeting your request. To make an access request, please email [admin@tickifieds.com](mailto:admin@tickifieds.com).

## 8\. Other information about your online privacy

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online (for example in ads that you post or through email) that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.

## 9\. How to contact Tickifieds

If you have any enquiries or wish to provide feedback about this policy, please email [admin@tickifieds.com](mailto:admin@tickifieds.com).

## Popular Events in this Category

| Ad Title | Event Date [](http://www.tickifieds.com/sorting/modify/item_search-showhtmllist-20576/dir/a/attr/col_11)[](http://www.tickifieds.com/sorting/modify/item_search-showhtmllist-20576/dir/d/attr/col_11)  
---|---|---  

|  [**Lady Gaga Meet and Greet Passes 2017 Wrigley Field**](http://www.tickifieds.com/mlb/national_league/chicago_cubs/228993_lady_gaga_meet_and_greet_passes_2017_wrigley_field) |  Fri August 25, 2017   
Meet LADY GAGA live before her historic show at Wrigley Field!! We have 4 VIP meet and greet passes available for the sold out show on 8/25/2017. Get them now before they are GONE!! Cheap Lady Gaga Tickets for sale! The ...   

|  [**Shawn Mendes VIP Meet and Greet Passes**](http://www.tickifieds.com/concerts_and_events/massachusetts/228702_shawn_mendes_vip_meet_and_greet_passes) |  Wed August 23, 2017   
Meet and Greet with Shawn Mendes - 08/23/2017 7:30PM - TD Garden - Boston, MA. WOW1!! 

Meet and Greet Deluxe Package includes: Meet and Greet with Shawn Mendes Premium reserved floor ticket ...   

|  [**Bruno Mars VIP MEET and GREET PASSES**](http://www.tickifieds.com/concerts_and_events/d_c/228704_bruno_mars_vip_meet_and_greet_passes) |  Fri September 29, 2017   
Bruno Mars VIP Meet and Greet Passes - 09/29/2017 8:00PM - Verizon Center - DC - Washington, DC 

Requires separate event ticket for use. These tickets are paperless. You will receive them at the venue on ...   

|  [**Buy Cheap JMBLYA 2017 - Austin featuring Chance The Rapper, Steve Aoki, Lil Uzi Vert, 6lack and more Tickets Austin 5/6/2017**](http://www.tickifieds.com/concerts_and_events/texas/229092_buy_cheap_jmblya_2017___austin_featuring_chance_the_rapper__steve_aoki__lil_uzi_vert__6lack_and_more_tickets_austin_5_6_2017) |  Sat May 06, 2017   
See JMBLYA 2017 - Austin featuring Chance The Rapper, Steve Aoki, Lil Uzi Vert, 6lack and more live from your seats in section General Admission at Circuit Of The Americas on 5/6/2017!! We have 3 premium tickets ...   

|  [**Bruno Mars 2017 Tickets - 24K Magic Tour**](http://www.tickifieds.com/concerts_and_events/california/228393_bruno_mars_2017_tickets___24k_magic_tour) |  Fri November 10, 2017   
See Bruno Mars live from your seats in section 202 at The LA Forum on 11/10/2017!! We have 4 premium tickets available in section 202 row TBD to see Bruno Mars at The LA Forum on 11/10/2017. Be a Bruno Mars VIP with these ...
